Guide to the Apple Computer, Inc. Records M1007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Research & Development, Series 3
  - Specifications, Subseries 3.6
    - Winchester controller, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Western Digital Corporation.
    - Macintosh Specifications, Box; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - MacPlus and Mac 512K Specifications, Box; 1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Floppy disk, Dept. 5831 product & budget information, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - 53C80 Specifications, Box; 1987 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      NCR Microelectronics
    - MacPlus, LaserWriter, Apple IIgs, etc. Specifications, Box; 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Leopard (object-oriented programming environment), 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Instantiations, Inc.
    - Engineering reference Specifications, Box documents (Apple IIgs) [1 of 2]; 1989, June (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Engineering reference Specifications, Box documents (Apple IIgs) [2 of 2]; 1989, June (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - System 5.0 release notes, 1989, June (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Initial evaluation of CD ROM drive, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Japanese language kit, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Technical information (Quadra 630), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Technical information (PowerBook 5300 series), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Technical information & RAM expansion card installation information (PowerBook Duo 2300c), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Technical information (PowerBook 190 series), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Technical information (Performa 640 series), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Twentieth Anniversary Macintosh, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Apple Spec Chart, 1996, Nov. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Preferred components mechanical manual, 1989 Aug. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Preferred components electrical manual, 1989 Aug. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Circuit schematic main logic PCB Apple II, 1978 July 19; Schematic 050-0006-00; 6 sheets of 6 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Circuit diagrams: Adam, Abel, ZyMos, B13, MMU, 1981 - 1982 (Box Nb5)
    - Circuit diagrams: Cain, 1982 - 1983 (Box Nb5)
    - Circuit diagrams: Aladdin, 1986 May (Box Nb5)
    - Circuit diagrams: Eve, Integrated disk controller, Integrated Woz machine, 1981 - 1982 (Box Nb5)
  - Newsletters, Subseries 3.7
    - Engineering Support Notice, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Floating in the Heap. No. 1 & 2, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Human Interface Notes., 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Standards, Box Notes.; 1985, Aug. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - System 7 Newsletter., 1991 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Tech Tidbits., 1990? (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Macintosh Reference & Information, Subseries 3.8
    - The Scrap Manager: a programmer's guide, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - TextEdit: a programmer's guide, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - The Event Manager: a programmer's guide, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - QuickDraw: a programmer's guide, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Inside Macintosh: a road map, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Macintosh Memory Management: an introduction, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Programming Macintosh Applications in Assembly Language, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - The Resource Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - The Resource Manager: a programmer's guide (one sheet), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - The Font Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - The Window Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - The Control Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The Menu Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - The Dialog Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - The Desk Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - The Toolbox Utilities: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Macintosh packages: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - The Memory Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - The Segment Loader: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - The File Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Printing from Macintosh Applications, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - The Device Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - The Sound Driver: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - The Vertical Retrace Manager: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - The Operating System Utilities: a programmer's guide, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - The Structure of a Macintosh Application, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Putting Together a Macintosh Application, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Index to Technical Documentation, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Mac Paslib Release V0.6, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      Chow, Yu-Ying
    - Supplement Update Errata, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Technical Communications to Tech Support Personnel (Macintosh), 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Technical Notes #0, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - A Software Developer's Guide to Switcher, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      Herzfeld, Andy
    - Switcher Instructions, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Tour Guide, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Power User Shortcut Summary (Macintosh), 1986 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - The Macintosh Family Hardware Reference, 1987, Mar. (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Sound Manager, System 6.0.2, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      Reekes, Jim
    - The Script Manager 2.0, 1989, Feb. (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Macintosh IIci Compatibility Report, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Integrating Macintosh into IBM Environments, 1990, May (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - QuickTime Technical Backgrounder, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Apple System 7 Q&A's, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Everything You Ever Wanted to Know About Upgrading to System 7, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - The first 20 things to do and notice with System Software 7.0, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Trouble Shooting (System 7.0), 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Product Orientation Guide (System 7), 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - At Ease 2.0 & At Ease 2.0 for Workgroups quick reference cards, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Paladin: Macintosh Personal Office Market Requirements documents, 1993, Jan. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Maven (internet audioconferencing tool for Macintosh), 1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Setting up your Macintosh Performa, 1994, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      English and French versions
    - Maslow! user experience requirements document, 1995, Oct. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - AIX, AppleTalk Services and the Network Server quick reference card, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Apple Media Tool quick reference card, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Quick Start Apple Color OneScanner Dispatcher Software reference card, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Reference & Information (general), Subseries 9
    - MOS technology information, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Dr. Dobb's Journal of Computer Calisthenics & Orthodontia. Vol. 1, No. 4., 1976, Apr. (Box 16, Folder 14)
      magazine
    - The New Creative Computing Catalogue, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Radio Shack Introduces The World of Computing, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - The First Blown Apple II Power Light, 1978, July (Box 16, Folder 17)
      Artifacts.
    - Commented source listing of interger BASIC, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      Avricchio, Rich
    - Fourth West Coast Computer Faire program, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Digital Research CP/M brochure, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
      Digital Research
    - Pascal Editor tutorial printout, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Personal Computers for the Physically Disabled: a resource guide, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Requirements for protection & control of electrostatic devices, 1981, Dec. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Apple terminator test results, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Pattern generator data, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      Horn, Mary; Bailey, Bob
    - A Note on the Personal Computer Industry, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      Brasso, Laura; University of Michigan; Powers, Dan
    - The Impact of the Microcomputer in the Business Environment, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      Newsweek
    - "Push" vs. "Pull", undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
      Pascoe, Geoff
    - ImageWriter pre-release notes for testers, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Future Views: a newsletter on emerging issues in the personal computing industry, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      McGraw-Hill
    - Information Appliances: A new industry, 1986, Feb. (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - A survey of business users of the Apple LaserWriter printer, 1986, Dec. (Box 16, Folder 32)
      Field Research Corporation
    - High-performance Automated Theorem-Proving Software, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - MIT Lab for Computer Science Research Groups, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Massachusetts Institute of Technology.
    - Floppy disk drives information, 1987, Oct. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Hard disk drives information, 1987, Oct. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Optical disk drive information, 1987, Nov. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Artificial Intelligence information, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Operating System Interest Group, 1987, June (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - HyperLego Leveraged Learning (Vivarium project), 1988, Apr. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Pink Display Architecture Overview, 1988, June. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Multimedia Production: casual production, videodisc basics, visual almanac, 1988, Nov. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - The Scores Virus, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - A Perspective on OOP Development Environments, 1988, Aug. (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Burbeck, Steve
    - What's so great about Mach?, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Smith, Walter
    - Competitive Product Bulletin, 1989, Mar. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Understanding Computer Networks, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - European Market Intelligence Mailing, 1989, Oct. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - AppleLink: summary of new features & improvements, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Independence Day: designing computer solutions for individuals with disability, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Competitive update, 1991 Dec. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Tiny Toons Release Notes, 1992, Mar. (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - The Vivarium Project, 1992, Aug. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - ATG Quick Reference Guide to Intellectual Property, Technical Reports & Research Notes and Publications, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - ATG External Research: Selected Project Reports, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Developing an information base on the OEM business of selected companies, 1993, Oct. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Warranty booklet (global), 1993? (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Apple Software License Agreement, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Client/Server Solutions: the roles of desktops, middleware and servers, 1994, July (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Technology Reference: what is client/server technology?, 1994, July (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Approaches to client/server integration, 1994, Aug. (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Operating in a netware world, 1994, Aug. (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - High speed networking/ IP, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Everything you need to know (but were afraid to ask kids) about the information highway, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Learning Communities Laboratory, 1996, Sept. (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Pricing & Troubleshooting Materials, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Apple Reference & Information, Subseries 3.10
    - Procedures (Apple II) [1 of 2], 1977 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Procedures (Apple II) [2 of 2], 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - System software AP[plication] notes (Apple II), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Personal computer competitive evaluation, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - At long last... Whatsit for Apple II, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Apple II Interface Notes #1, 1979, Feb. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - A brief introduction to the new Pascal, 1979, Oct. (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Kellner, Charlie; Hoffman, Al; McMaster, Colin
    - notes on designing Apple II/III power supply, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Holt, Rod
    - Apple III Business Graphics Reference Card, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Preliminary NROFF documentation, version 6.5, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      McMaster, Colin
    - Apple Software Bank Application Notes (Apple II) [1 of 2], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Apple Software Bank Application Notes (Apple II) [2 of 2], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Apple Answer Book (reprint of Vol. 1), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Apple Answer Book 2 (Apple II/III), 1981? (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Apple IIe project binder, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Technical Support Training (student manual) [1 of 2], 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Technical Support Training (student manual) [2 of 2], 1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Technical Support Training (instructor manual), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Apple II Forever College Binder [1 of 2], 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Apple II Forever College Binder [2 of 2], 1985 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Color Truth Table, 1985, Feb. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Baker, Gary
    - BASIC reserved words & formats converter chart (machine/ Microsoft), 1986 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      PC World
    - Apple II Software Emulators, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Lisa Reference & Information, Subseries 3.11
    - Lisa SmallTalk-80 Version 1.0, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Programmer's Handbook [1 of 2], 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Programmer's Handbook [2 of 2], 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Programmer's Handbook [1 of 3], 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Programmer's Handbook [2 of 3], 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Programmer's Handbook [3 of 3], 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Technical communications [re: LISA], 1983 Apr. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - TK5C Toolkit Listings [1 of 2], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - TK5C Toolkit Listings [2 of 2], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Lisa Localization Kit [1 of 2], 1983, Oct. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Lisa Localization Kit [1 of 2], 1983, Oct. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - SANELib: release V0.5, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Lisa Workshop Supplement Version 1.0, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Reports, Subseries 3.12
    - Project report & worksheet forms, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - New products review, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Charters: corporate engineering services & technical information services/ library, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Minutes of Engineering Council Meeting, 1982, Dec. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Macintosh ROM Overview & Product Illustrations, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Logian manual and information about expert systems and learning, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - ATG reports, agendas, etc. (misc.), 1986-1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - AAAI 1987 (brief summary), 1987, July (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Living Museum (HyperCard project), 1987 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Report on Fabrik, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - MCC Expert Systems Technology, 1987? (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Human Interface Lab presentation, 1987? (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Fabrik project, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - MIT Media Laboratory, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Applex Project report, 1988, June (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Applex info, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      Loofbourrow, Wayne
    - student design projects flyer invitation, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Viruses and the Macintosh (technical support executive summary), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Project Collaboration: a distributed hypermedia prototype-- project plan, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      Chesley, Harry R.
    - HyperCard MIDI interface meeting, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      Holm, Mike
    - Integrated learning design: project summaries, 1990, May (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Hard drive 20/40 pricing/ upgrade proposal, 1990? (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Artificial intelligence project papers, 1990? (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - ATG progress Reports, Box; 1990, Mar. - June (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Introduction to the Apple-Digital network environment, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Pacific Research & Development Bible: status (software, CPU, peripherals), 1991, Oct. (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Mandala Project presentation materials, MindTop Project (world's smallest computer), 1991 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      Kawasaki, Kazuo
    - San Francisco Apple Multimedia Lab, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - PowerPC technology: the power behind the next generation of Macintosh systems, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - external research Reports, Box; 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - FrameRelay: what is it and why is it important?, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Wireless LANs: the basics of radio frequency technology, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Wireless WANs: the basics of paging technology, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Apple Workgroup Server 95: a multi-threading A/UX system, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Personal Communications Systems/ personal communications systems and how they work, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Bridging the gap (telephony), 1995? (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Apple Speech Program & Apple Speech Technology Q&A, 1995? (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - A look inside the color LaserWriter: color without compromise, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - A look inside the AppleVision display, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - PowerMacintosh: the next step, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - PowerPC hardware reference platform, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Corporate Library, Series 4
  This series includes information on planned Apple Museum and Apple Archives as well as the Apple Library User Group and files on libraries that received Apple products for special project work.
  - Apple Library User Group (ALUG) Newsletters, Subseries 4.1
    - ALUG Newsletter. Vol. 1 No. 1., Vol. 2 Nos. 1-4, Vol. 3 Nos. 1-4, Vol. 4 Nos. 1-4, Vol. 5 Nos. 1-3, Vol 6 Nos. 1-2, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 18)
    - ALUG Newsletter. Vol 6 Nos. 3-4, Vol. 7 Nos. 1-4, Vol. 8 Nos. 1-3, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1 - 9)
  - Macintoshed Libraries, Subseries 4.2
    - ALUG Newsletter. Vol. 9 No. 4, Vol. 10 Nos. 1-3, Vol. 11 Nos. 1-4, Vol. 12 Nos. 1-4, Vol. 13 Nos. 1-4, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1 - 10)
    - The Macintoshed Library: uses of the Apple Macintosh in a special library, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Valauskas, Edward J.
    - Macintoshed Libraries ([1], 3.0, 4.0, 5.0, 6.0), 1988-1994 (Box 3, Folder 12 - 16)
      Valauskas, Edward J. Vaccaro, Bill
  - Template Exchange, Subseries 4.3
    - Apple Library Template Exchange, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Template Exchange information, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Apple Library of Tomorrow (ALOT), Subseries 4.4
    - Proceedings: Community Networking Conference, 1996, May (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ALOT, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 4 - 8)
      Cisler, Steve
    - ALOT/ ALUG mailing list [?], undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - ALOT conference comment sheets, 1989? (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - ALOT project summary sheets, 1991? (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - ALOT equipment requests, 1990? (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - press clippings, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - ALOT conference, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - information on community networking, var. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Apple employees who helped with ALOT, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - insitution-specific project proposals, requests and reports, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 6 - 16)
      some diskettes included
      San Francisco State University; Smithsonian Institution; North Carolina State University; Beloit College; Northwestern University (Evanston, Ill.); Hopkinton High School; University of California, Berkeley.; Memex; Denver Public Library; Telecoms; Hans Helgesen Elementary School
    - insitution-specific project proposals, requests and reports, 1989-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1 - 21)
      some diskettes & photos included
      Mendocino County Library; Lowell School; University of Wisconsin at River Falls; University of Toronto; Hart, Michael S. (Project Gute; Ft. Collins (CO) Public Library; Delaware State Libraries; Liverpool (NY) Public Library; Zimmerman, Mark; Catawba-Wateree Health Education Center; Yale; Conestoga Senior High School; Contra Costa COunty Library; Zuni; Coston Elementary School; Whitman County (WA); Washington State University; Wisconsin Interlibrary Services; Americans for Indian Opportunities; William Penn Charter School; California State Library
    - insitution-specific project proposals, requests and reports, 1989-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1 - 14)
      National Agricultural Library; National Commission on Libraries & Information Science; Ohio Valley Area Libraries; Rennselaer Polytechnic Institute; Library of Congress (American Memory project); Juvenile Justice Center School; San Francisco Public Library; Los Gatos Memorial Library; Hawaii INC; Sooke School; Louisville (KY) Free Public Library; Medina County (OH) Free-Net
    - insitution-specific project proposals, requests and reports, 1988-1993 (Box 8, Folder 1 - 4)
      University of Alaska - Fairbanks (Project Jukebox); Telluride Institute; Rogers, Fred; University of Pittsburgh (PA) (Mr. Rogers Collection); University of Michigan
    - Ties that bind: building community networks, 1994, May (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - ALOT projects 1990-1992, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Ties that bind: converging communities, 1995, May (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Apple Library User Group, Subseries 4.5
    - Directory of librarians using Macintoshes, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ALUG logo correspondence, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Justie, Kevin
    - ALUG press info, 1988-1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - ALUG correspondence, 1983-1986, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Ertel, Monica
    - ALUG meeting in San Francisco, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - ALUG meeting in Atlanta, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - ALUG meeting in Dallas, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      photos
    - ALUG meeting in New York, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - ALUG meeting in Chicago, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - local ALUG meetings, 1986-1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - ALUG online, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Files, Subseries 4.6
    - Where is the Macintosh library?, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Lukos, Garry; Boston Macintosh Users Group
    - Getting a handle on knowledge, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Apple II Bibliophile, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - List of Marketing Materials, 1987? (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - library management memos, organization charts, etc., 1985-1995 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - CD ROM survey, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ALOT, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      includes cd
    - reference & trivia, var. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - workshops & training produced by Apple library, var. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Get Info... Apple Library Newsletter, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - library staff photos, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Askew, Kathy; Singer, Marcia; Bercik, Mary Ellen; Reding, Bill; Oros, Jane; Cisler, Steve; Echeandia, Pedro; Bidwell, Lynne; Broun, Kevin; Hawley, Lorin; Lau, Pam; Ertel, Monica; Vratny-Watts, Janet; Gilman, Greg; McKinney, Joanne; Mead, Dale; Macek, Rosanne; Mason, Terri
    - library move, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - software collection issues, 1982-1985? (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - conference, meeting & trip reports, 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Intel Museum information, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Apple museum, 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Apple archives, 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      includes "Plan for an Apple Archives" proposal by Lewis (archivist at Hewett-Packard)
      Lewis, Karen R.
    - Apple Library Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - articles, var. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - collected mission statements from other corporate libraries, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Apple Library Systems Project: Strategic Plan Goal 1, Analysis & Recommendations, 1994, Dec. (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Here's how to use... Personal Apple Library, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)